<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[ParticleQuest Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-23T23:13:29+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[ParticleQuest Team]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginning]]></title>
    <link href="http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/2012/12/the-beginning/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-23T21:09:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/2012/12/the-beginning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Let&#8217;s share a little bit of history. It all began as an idea of <a href="https://twitter.com/teleyinex">Daniel Lombraña</a> for the <a href="http://www.citizencyberscience.net/cern-webfest/">CERN Summer Student Webfest</a> last Summer. Wouldn&#8217;t forking BrowserQuest to teach particle physics be a great idea?</p>

<p>During the hackathon, <a href="https://twitter.com/jessykate">Jessy Kate</a> took the lead and other four followed her to start working on the project ParticleQuest. Thanks to the multicultural environment of CERN, among the team there were people from Canada, France, Philippines and Spain.</p>

<p><img src="http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/ParticleQuest/images/img/2012-12-23-the-beginning.jpg"></p>

<p>After the weekend it turned out that the jury found ParticleQuest deserved the first prize (yay!) and thus our next step was the Mozilla Festival 2012 in London. But we&#8217;ll talk about that in the next post.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello world!]]></title>
    <link href="http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/2012/12/hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-16T22:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://OmeGak.github.com/ParticleQuest/2012/12/hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re alive in the blogverse!</p>

<p>From now on we&#8217;ll be posting here our progress throughout the development of the project. Expect us to start with a few posts to catch up with everything that has been going on with ParticleQuest since the beginning.</p>

<p>Just to summarize and spoil some of the upcoming posts, at the moment, we, <a href="http://twitter.com/OmeGak">@OmeGak</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/L4D15">@L4D15</a>, are participating in the <a href="http://www.concursosoftwarelibre.org/1213/">CUSL</a>, an open source contest, with ParticleQuest. This was pretty much the main motivation for us to work on the project, besides for the fun of hacking, but CERN showed interest in it and Mozilla suggested us to participate in the <a href="https://gameon.mozilla.org/en-US/">GameOn</a> as well, so this is just the start a long journey!</p>

<p>One final announce. The DNS are not updated yet but you will be able to access the blog at <a href="http://blog.particlequest.com">http://blog.particlequest.com</a> pretty soon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
